<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Russell Ijaya</title>
    <link>https://rijaya273.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Russell Ijaya</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://rijaya273.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>exploring single sign-on design</title>
      <link>https://rijaya273.github.io/publicsecure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rijaya273.github.io/publicsecure/</guid>
      <description>-- Understanding establishing context The currently deployed sign-on systems, ONe-key and Public Secure Pilot, have not met the expectations of the Ontario government&amp;rsquo;s program areas, as shown by high call centre volumes and low adoption rates of digital services. From that point of understanding, we then conducted research with program area stakeholders and members of the public to tangibly define existing problems and public expectations respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>reimagining the renter experience</title>
      <link>https://rijaya273.github.io/zumper-redesign/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rijaya273.github.io/zumper-redesign/</guid>
      <description>--                 Product exploration emphasizing contextual problem solving While the stress, excitement and emotional complexities of finding a place to live in are hard to emulate without first-hand experience, performing a deep dive into listing exploration features and a few too many NYC apartment hunting YouTube videos allowed me to grasp the problem Zumper is trying to solve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>designing for mental health inclusion</title>
      <link>https://rijaya273.github.io/collective/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rijaya273.github.io/collective/</guid>
      <description>--                 Problem Discovery finding a door to open To begin learning what questions to ask, we started by breaking down the challenge prompt:
While we did look at other subspaces involving the inclusion of groups with disabilities, we eventually decided on exploring the barriers to inclusion for those with mental health disabilities after coming across the following, solidifying the problem&amp;rsquo;s existence:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>